Adamus has led to an explosion in CPU
related stocks and boy there are a lot
of opportunities in the stock market
more so than just Meta Stock and AMD
which absolutely crushed today. Uh today
you've got AMD up 9.95%
officially a 1 trillion market cap. We
had a call on this stock when it was at
$452
and told course members, folks, this
puppy's about to bounce off this line.
Juicy. Did not expect it to go this high
this fast. So, that's what happens with
the market. The market can move fast.
You got six figures almost multiple
probably multiple figures at this point
of exposure to Meta. Uh you've got a
delicious bounce off of the legendary
544 line and a breakout on the downtrend
here. Glorious move on Meta up 11.4%.
And so a lot of folks are wondering what
other stocks are there and is it too
late? Uh well in this segment we're
going to go through other stock
opportunities and we're going to look at
exactly what's going on. So, the first
thing that you've got to know is all of
this AI chatbot stuff in my opinion is
an opportunity for advertisers. And I'm
just pulling up the app store right now
because what I find when I open up the
app store uh is I tend to find ads for
Metam Muse and they continue to pop up
for me. What I think is advertising is a
critical place to get exposure for these
apps, all this sort of AI competition.
Now, that's going to be a small
component of what we touch on in this
video, but something you have to watch
for is the more agents browse products
for you, the less human eyeballs are on
them. So whether it's Door Dash or
Wingstop or some form of even Amazon
Shop Store, which is exactly why Amazon
is now banning the Metam Muse app from
crawling their website, you actually
have fewer humans looking at those
websites and therefore you drive up the
value of advertisements in app stores
where humans are actually going to go
download things, which is a benefit to
Apple or a benefit to Google for where
people are watching entertaining
content, whether it's Netflix,
entertainment content, whether it's
Netflix, uh, or it's YouTube. For some
reason, I can't get the app store open
right now. I keep getting the stupid,
uh, it's classic Apple. I type in app to
get to get my apps to come up and I I
only get Google Apple, but it's or the,
uh, the Apple store to go buy the iPhone
Duo. I think it's a sign, but it doesn't
matter. I am finding that a lot of these
apps are competing with each other for
ads space. So, you're seeing Metamus's
advertising inside of the app store.
You're seeing GPT advertise in there.
And what's happening? Oh, there we go.
What's happening is you have this
competition to get users. You've even
got Gemini now advertising. They're all
advertising. So, you open up the app
store today, Google Gemini running apps.
Earlier that was Metamuse. They're
cycling through them. Chat GPT is in
there. If you go to the top free now uh
and you go to the top uh essential apps
under the free category, you'll find
that MetaMuse is now at the top on the
free chart which has blown past chat GPT
at now number two. And then you've got
prediction markets at four and five. You
don't actually see Gemini until 8. You
don't even see Claude from Anthropic
until all the way down here at number
16, which is insane. Instagram is at 18.
Metamuse made it to one. Now, part of
the reason I bring up advertisers is
because it's not just ads that they're
running on these platforms, whether it's
the app stores or otherwise. They're
also running billboards. They're buying
influencer campaign spots. These apps
are competing to get as many users
hooked into the platform as possible. I
actually think or as many users as
possible. And I actually think that's
going to be a boon for advertisers and
advertising stocks. is actually one of
the reasons that I bought Meta because I
thought, okay, well, Meta Stock is not
only an advertiser paying for their AI
development, but they are also a
beneficiary of the GPUs that they're
buying, the over 4 gawatts of compute
they have. The value of those GPUs has
only gone up. And they're a beneficiary
of AI productivity, which their Muse
launch is incredible. And we don't even
have the watermelon release yet, which
is expected next month for their
Frontier language model, their Frontier
LLM. So, what other stocks could
benefit? Well, outside of these that
we've just mentioned, I think
advertisers have an opportunity. Whether
it's Google or it's something like an
app loving, Netflix, I think those have
opportunities as well. though let's go a
little bit more clear and indepth into
like AMD and Intel themselves plus some
others in the actual hardware space. So,
first you got to know when you're
advertising these
agents, they're a little different from
GPUs uh and chat bots. Usually, when we
think GPUs, we're thinking training and
uh uh responding to larger context sets
with chat bots uh and operating, how
should we put it, uh at the frontier.
So, our latest Reuben chip, for example,
is massively 10xing bandwidth
capabilities over and above the hardware
capabilities of something like an H100
chip that uh Nvidia used to operate. And
LLMs have been trying to buy as many
GPUs as they can get their hands on. But
there are a lot of processes that
operate really efficiently in artificial
intelligence on CPUs.
One of those happens to be an agentic
workload and that's essentially what
Metamuse is. So that's why now you've
got a lot of folks running to CPU stocks
instead of GPUs. Now we operate a bunch
of CPUbased machines for the AI that we
operate over at Reinvest. So as a
startup, we've been seeing the writing
on the wall for many months. Since about
March, we've been seeing this transition
to more and more CPUs, which is exactly
why Nvidia got into the play. And a lot
of people forget that Nvidia, while it's
our core sort of GPU play, Nvidia is
expecting to blow up their CPU
competition for a pure play or more pure
play like AMD. Although AMD also
provides GPUs. Let's talk about some of
the numbers here. So Nvidia is
projecting $20 billion of CPU demand in
calendar year 2026 alone. 20 billion of
just CPU demand alone would rival right
now about three quarters of gross profit
that AMD actually makes already. So it's
kind of interesting, but a lot of people
don't look at Nvidia as a CPU play. And
I think that's why in part Nvidia is
lagging a little bit. Take a look at
this. Nvidia just today recaptured the
727 line, which is great. We called that
out this morning on our alpha report. We
also called out Meta breaking through uh
to breaking up to 700 this week and it
went all the way up to 741, which blew
my mind. I was looking for 700. We wrote
that down. We actually made a coupon
code in honor of this called Metaballs
that's only going to last for 12 hours.
Actually, now it's probably more like 10
hours. We're expiring it tonight and
we're officially doing our $900 price
increase. But these were the calls we
made this morning in the alpha report.
Peak fear was 2 weeks ago. If 725 holds
and Nvidia holds 720, so 725 on the Q's
hold and Nvidia holds uh 720, we are
going up. We'll be back at 735 soon. We
nailed it. We blew through to 741 on the
Q's, which was remarkable. We had our
durability test on Friday. We had meta.
We called for 700. Even though on
Friday, and I even said it Friday on a
public video, I'm like, man, it's at 666
and I have a price target of 700 by next
Friday. Dude, it's at 741 on Monday. I'm
like, dang, this is freaking crazy. Uh,
we did make the observation that Hood
was testing the 127 line. Uh, this
wasn't a play I was really looking at,
but I did mention it, so I put it in
here as a miss. And then our next two
that we're really looking at are bullish
buying the dip between now and midterms
and then I think we'll hit all-time
highs by Black Friday. We're actually
only 1% now from all-time highs. So I
feel like this is already a little bit
dated, but like we were rightfully
optimistic here and I'd love for you to
be part of the alpha membership, but you
could join over at meetke.com. Would
love to see you there. We've got a lot
to talk about tomorrow morning in our
alpha report in addition to the analysis
that we do. But look at some of this
analysis. So, if Nvidia is forecasting
uh
how should I put it, $20 billion of CPU
compute sales by the end of 2026. It's
worth noting that the total sales that
AMD has in 3 months set at about 11.5.
So Nvidia is looking at doing about 6
months worth of AMD sales on a sector
they basically had zero revenue at a
year ago which actually makes AMD or
sorry makes Nvidia a real competitor to
AMD in the CPU space. Now I'm not trying
to bag on AMD. I think there's still
opportunity in AMD. I mean just think
about even the benchmarks alone their
Helios system you're looking at versus
the re Vera Rubin 50% more high
bandwidth memory 50% more scaleout
bandwidth and about 10 to 15% more
tokens per second so the Helios rack has
been a great product versus Vera Rubin
especially since people are wanting
these CPUs right now so they've got a
really good quality product and on some
benchmarks AMD does actually beat Nvidia
GPUs. The Vera portion of the Vera
Rubin, their epic Turin Fifth generation
chip is right now projected to get to
about 50% of all CPU TAM, total
addressable market in data centers. And
that's why people are going nuts here
because this is an x86 product, which
means you're not paying the ARM
licensing fees. ARM stock was up quite a
bit today because you have companies
like Apple, another beneficiary of the
CPU movement. By the way, remember
OpenAI bought tens of thousands of Apple
and Mac Studios and Mac minis for a
gentic artificial intelligence as OpenAI
bought those from Apple and ARM licenses
the uh architecture on which these CPUs
are programmed. So, their stock was
actually up 17% today. Not a lot of
people actually talking about ARM
relative to AMD. AMD sits at about a
$344 billion market cap, but also a
competitor. The more you get Nvidia and
Apple taking off on CPU competition for
AMD. So AMD is doing x86, that's your
Intel style, Intel Corporation was up
like 14% today, ended up 12%. So AMD,
think x86 and Intel. Apple as a CPU
play, think ARM chips. And then of
course think Apple itself also a
beneficiary of advertisers on the app
store.
Nvidia coming in to try to get some
access to this TAM as well because they
see the writing on the wall to move
towards agentic artificial intelligence
opportunities.
Now their target is to get to 50% CPU by
2030. Again right now they're a little
bit lower than that. They're in the
high30s.
They're expecting to grow revenue
remarkably though. You got 72% revenue
growth projected at AMD between now and
next year. And they'll get to 88 billion
of revenue for the entire year is the
projection. If you compare $88 billion
for the entire year to just the revenue
that Nvidia makes from data centers,
Nvidia makes an entire AMD in revenue in
one quarter. So it's worth knowing the
comparison of the players. Now, Nvidia
is five times the size per market cap
compared to AMD. We'll have some more
comparisons between them, but this is
why people think if the next frontier is
CPUs and Nvidia is a $5 trillion
company, what's stopping AMD from being
able to rise as well. And Nvidia sees
this writing on the wall, hence why
they're also getting into CPUs, which is
why Nvidia is also a CPU player to
consider. So, you've got AMD, Intel,
you've got ARM, Apple, obviously Meta,
which is driving this insanity today.
And then Nvidia, what else do we have?
And then we'll go through some more of
these numbers so you could get a little
bit more perspective. I just don't want
to get too lost in the weeds of numbers
because sometimes numbers get a little
boring. But let's consider for a moment
who else you have to consider.
Obviously, Intel. We talked about them,
but why do we care about Intel? Because
Intel is projected to double their CPU
sales between 26 to 27, potentially
frankly both years. Their data center
and AI revenue in the second quarter of
2026 was already up 59% from a year ago.
And that was only on 9% more units,
which is crazy. So you delivered 9% more
CPUs, but your pricing is up to make up
the difference 48%.
That's pricing power. So, Intel is
seeing pricing power as well. So, not
only are they a manufacturer, but
they're also a chip designer
manufacturing their own CPUs. So, it's a
big win for Intel as well. And of
course, we're super supply constrainted
at all ends. And this is where Nvidia
actually has a little bit of an
advantage. Uh, and so I I don't want to
talk too much about Nvidia here. I've
got exposure to a lot of the different
stocks we're mentioning here, so I'm not
short on anything. I'm pretty bullish
right now. I just want to be clear like,
you know, I try to put my biases out
there. I've I've got exposure to this
kind of stuff, okay? But I want you to
see the commitments or or the commitment
differences between these companies
because I think it's important. AMD has
commitments between now and the end like
2031 and after. Most of the commitments
are up front here. AMD has commitments
of about $30 billion. that those are
commitments for they say right here to
purchase wafers, substrates, and
components from third parties. You need
components to actually make CPUs, you
you got to have the input supply, right?
So, they've got their hands on about $30
billion of commitments.
Nvidia, though, has $334
billion in commitments in roughly the
same time, in the same time frame. So
this means Nvidia has 11x the supply on
lock and they're 5x the company. Again,
I think this is where you could see this
is not this is not going to be a single
horse race. This is going to be a
multi-seor race where they are grabbing
as much supply as they can for both CPUs
and GPUs. In fairness for Nvidia, a lot
of this is going to be part of memory. A
lot of this is also going to be part of
their GPU business. But memory is very
important. I mean, if I pull up memory
expectations right now, I've got a
screenshot right here uh for just
pricing. Uh oh, this is actually on
CPUs. This is CPU pricing. Intel CEO CEO
highlights a severe supply shortage in
server CPUs with Intel's existing
capacity fulfilling only 50% of actual
customer demand. According to reports,
Intel will raise PC CPU prices by about
10%. and expect even more of a price
increase for data center ones. The
reason there's a difference there is
these are different lines, different
qualities of products. The CPU market
for PCs relatively weak. Gaming is
actually in decline at most of the
manufacturing uh or designers and
manufacturers including Nvidia. But
what's rocketing are data centers. So,
the fact that Intel is raising pricing
on consumer CPUs is actually surprising,
but it just shows you how severe the
shortage is. Anyway, DRAM prices aren't
really expected to peak until late next
year. So, memory prices are still going
up. This is why you have AMD and Nvidia
jumping on this bandwagon of trying to
secure as much compute as they can now.
And when I say compute, in this case, I
mean DRAM and components to secure their
compute output. But Nvidia is doing it.
You know, they're they're getting twice
as much size adjusted as AMD is probably
because they have more of a capacity to
pay and and they're able to write bigger
checks essentially. I do think that's an
interesting comparison where I also
think it's interesting to look at the uh
actual income statement of the two
companies just so you could see the
margin and the margin growth that's
occurring. AMD's margins have
skyrocketed. We've gone from 36 or sorry
39.8% margins to 53.7%.
That's really good. But it's worth
noting Nvidia is sitting at 75%
gross. And AMD just came out of a loss
with a 17.2% net. Nvidia is bringing to
their bottom line 63%.
So the numbers are like massively
different. Operating income in three
months at AMD was just $2 billion. If I
go to the income statement and I look at
operating income for Nvidia, you are
sitting at $63 billion. That's 30x the
operating income in a quarter over at
Nvidia. And and I say this not to say
like, oh, Nvidia is better. I'm saying
this is why the market thinks there's so
much upside for AMD.
But in doing so, I feel I do feel like
Nvidia is also getting a little bit left
behind. like it hasn't been part of the
party. Nvidia's valuation is dirt cheap
right now. You're talking about a
valuation that is a fraction uh of AMD's
valuation. AMD right now at at the price
it just ran to is trading for about a
1.5 to 1.6 peg ratio. Nvidia is trading
at about a one or about a.7.
So you are more than two times as
expensive at AMD right now as you are at
Nvidia. Is it possible then that either
Nvidia catches up or AMD slows down?
Maybe. I'm not calling for that. Like I
wouldn't place a short bet on it. Uh and
the reason is we're getting a little
overbought. And like the reason that
could be desirable is we're getting
overbought. I'm not saying it's time to
sell it. I I'm not going to short it.
But if you look on the day chart, you
are well overbought on a AMD right now
at almost 73 on the relative strength
index. And on a weekly basis, you just
crossed 70 to 70.1. So, a little
extreme. And if you compare that to
Nvidia, I haven't done this yet. Let's
go take a look at it. Nvidia's mid-range
on the week at about 59 and about 58 on
the day. So, you can kind of see on a
relative strength basis how Nvidia is
getting left behind. What's really been
running has been AMD and like Dell.
Okay, Dell mostly for that onprem
CPU and GPU deployment. Pretty
impressive. Okay, let's keep going here.
So, uh, going back to Intel for a moment
since we're jumping around here. Data
center customers are going nuts for CPUs
in part because of Agentic AI. We know
that Capex is exploding at Intel just
like it is at almost all of the
infrastructure plays. Whether you're
looking at Meta, who still has 15
billion of free cash flow, which is
actually remarkable that they still have
that. Uh, but Intel is like your
expensive manufacturing buildout where
you're taking all the money you're
making and you're throwing it into
building out this manufacturing process.
AMD doesn't have to do that because AMD
can manufacture with Intel or Taiwan
Semi. And the benefit of this is AMD is
almost certainly always going to be a
higher margin play than Intel. Something
to think about. It's not bagging on
Intel. That's just a comparison. ARM is
though also pretty dang high margin
because ARM is probably going to get to
somewhere around 17 to 18% of total CPU
TAM and I think they're going to grow
that to 40 to 50% and you'll be like one
in one in competition with AMD for uh
x86 architectures because ARM is going
to be the product of choice likely to
stay this way for Apple and Nvidia and
they are coming for the CPU market.
Everybody knows there's so much money to
be made in CPUs, so the competition is
coming. The pure play in fairness right
now, AMD and Intel, and I think that's
why they've done so freaking well right
now. Uh, regarding partnerships though,
and this I think is very interesting.
Well, you've got Apple and Nvidia with
ARM. Google's doing a chip. Uh, Axion
with ARM. You've got AWS Graviton.
You've got Microsoft Cobalt. All of
those are ARMbased. You've also uh uh
got ARM partnering with Broadcom and
Qualcomm. They're partnering all over
the place. AMD does also have some
upside partnerships. Take a look at
this.
AMD offered call options known on a
company to company basis as Warrants to
Meta and OpenAI. So, this means Meta on
the skyrocketing of AMD shares is
probably now going to have to recognize
a profit on their call options on uh
AMD, which allow them to buy AMD at one
penny per share. And they get to
exercise that anytime between October
5th, 2030
uh and between now and October 5th, 2030
for OpenAI and now through February
23rd, 2031 for Meta.
So you do have Lisa Sue going out to
companies like Meta and OpenAI saying,
"Hey, can you guys go buy six gigawatts
worth of our chips in exchange? We are
going to give you shares." that is
dilutive but in fairness it's just a
different form of circular financing
compared to what Nvidia does which is
investing directly into companies the
extra cash flow that they have which
they have much more than AMD to give uh
and then creating demand as a result of
that look over here this is the cash
flow statement for Nvidia cash flow
statement on Nvidia if I look at right
here purchases of equity and debt
securities they have literally bought
$42 billion worth of other people's
equity or 40 or $21 billion of other
people's debt in literally six months
ending July 20th. Their cash flow is $70
billion of free cash flow. AMD can't
pull that off. Like they just they just
don't have those assets. If you look at
their free cash flow, they're at $4
billion in six months. That is Nvidia's
17.5
times richer on cash flow. So instead,
AMD is like, "We'll just take our
clothes off. We'll just give you some of
our shares instead. So, you know, we
can't do a service for you. We'll just
take our clothes. We'll give it to you
in a different way, basically." Okay,
that's fine. AMD doesn't have the
margins that Nvidia does, but it's
trying to get there. That's the whole
point. Again, we already went through
these margins right here. 62% net
compared to 17% at AMD. That's the
growth side. People think Nvidia is
basically topped on margins and topped
on, you know, how much they can access.
But people forget that Nvidia has this
whole CPU business that's starting from
zero coming to compete with AMD.
Remember, 20 billion of CPU sales from
Nvidia are expected in sort of a full
stack sale where even if we double data
center sales right now, we go over here
and let's say we double and annualize
this. So let's take data center in a
quarter of 6.6. 7. Let's go 6.7 * 4.
That's 26.8 billion. And then let's just
double it. Okay, let's just be really
generous. That would be 53 billion of
CPU sales in 2027.
Nvidia is expecting to sell 20 billion
in 2026. Let's say they grow that by
50%. That would be 30 billion.
AMD is actually got or AMD actually has
competition coming right up their butt
for those CPUs and it's Jensen. He
doesn't want to be out outbeat by Lisa
and I get, you know, they're related,
which is even the craziest part. But
it's it's like a neck andneck horse
race. It's really entertaining to see
this, but AMD is going to be a big
beneficiary of of increasing margins.
And you actually see that comment right
here. Look at this. uh AMD Instinct
which is their GPU product was recorded
in the prior year uh or or a greater mix
of those which led to uh higher data
center revenue and therefore a favorable
product mix for margins in English their
margins went up because of these
products like more data center sales duh
you're going to make more selling to
data centers than you are selling to
consumers duh now again like this is the
kind of analysis by the way that we try
to do in the alpha membership if not
part of it yet, remember, go to meet
Kevin.com and join us. You get all nine
courses. You get the alpha report every
single day. People are leaving comments
in the chat going, "The alpha membership
paid for itself in like one trade."
Obviously, I can't guarantee or vet
that, but that sounds really cool. Uh
these are just some of the calls that we
made in the alpha report today. Uh you
know, backing off of also all the calls
that we made on Friday. And so we are
going to um uh throw a $900 price
increase in net uh into the alpha
membership. So you may as well get in
today before midnight. Uh and that's
coupon code meta balls if you go to
meetc.com. We were changing the price
and then we look at Meta Stock. We're
like I don't know. Should we do a flash
sale? So we're doing a flash sale on it.
It's a win for you. It's a win for us.
It's a win for Reinvest. Everybody wins.
You know how bad is that? Okay. Let's
keep looking at this. AMD has also
acquired a company called ZT Group that
helps enable more generalpurpose compute
infrastructure for hyperscaling
computing companies. In English, yo, we
are increasing our sex appeal for them
data centers cuz the margins is good,
dog. It doesn't have to just be one
winner here. This is a big W for AMD. I
get a little concern like I don't I have
to be transparent. I would not add to
AMD at this place. It could keep going.
It just right now it feels a little
toasty and a little euphoric.
I think there are other opportunities.
There are a bunch of them whether it's
Apple. Apple's a little pricey. You can
look at some of the ASIC manufacturers
or I should say designers because most
of them use um what's it called? Uh TSM
to manufacture one that I do not own
this. Okay. I do not own this one I'm
about to show you. So I'm not I I I
think it's important to share your bias.
I I think most people don't do that
enough. I I the last thing I want
somebody to do is think, "Oh, Kevin's
talking his book or whatever." I all my
stocks could go to zero, it doesn't
matter. Now, if all my real estate goes
to zero, I'd cry,
but I don't think that's going to
happen. I think we bought real estate in
really good places. Uh but anyway,
Broadcom, dude, it it is right on the
355 line. It's recaptured 355, but this
is the next boomer right here in my
opinion. This is the ne you really want
to pay attention to this. Cerebrus I
also think has hit a floor. I don't own
Broadcom. I've got exposure to Cerebrus.
Not a lot, a little bit. You know, you
sort of DCA into that one. I think that
one became a buy under about 250. So 250
and below. I think Cerebrus is a buy. I
don't think it's going to stay there
long. Robotics, that's the next place.
Forget about agents for a moment.
Robotics, you want Cerebrus and you want
Nvidia. Those are your big robotics
plays. And there are many more. We've
got them in the research tab of the
stock app that other companies that
benefit from robotics. But those are two
really juicy plays. Okay, what else do
we have? So, uh, let's be clear about
this. Muse is going parabolic. It
launched on September 8th. It's been
like two weeks that this has been out
and so it's doing really well. It's
sending emails for people, booking
travel. I haven't tried the desktop app
yet, but apparently it's also got a
desktop app. I've only been using the uh
mobile app. That's pretty good.
advertisers here when we talked about
that uh we made a call on Meta on August
28th that this stock was about to
skyrocket and it did. We made that call
when it was at about $566.
I mean you could just look you go look
at my video type into YouTube meet Kevin
Meta stock is about to skyrocket and
watch the video August 28th a lot of
detail over here. It was right there. It
wasn't like a particularly juicy day or
whatever. I mean, the stock moved 027
that day. You know, two days later it
was down. Whatever. But, uh, but the
skyrocket still clearly came.
This still has opportunities. We're
talking so much about AMD and Nvidia,
and I don't want people to forget that
Meta, in my opinion, is still dirt
cheap. The next stop here is 8.26. We
did make a temporary line over here at
7:32, but we did smoke that line already
today. I don't even think we stopped at
that line. Yeah. So, so far that line is
a failure. We drew that today as like a
maybe. No, so far that one's looking
bad. Uh 735 on QQQ was another one that
we absolutely smashed today. And we did
at least get a generous pit stop at my
line. It's another gray line, so it's
not perfect, but we got a generous stop
right there. But 700 was glorious.
Should upgrade that line. That one was
great. We bought the dip on 700 and sent
a buy alert to everybody on that one,
too. Uh, what else do we need to know?
So, Muse for Mac, uh, and a bunch of
third party Oh, did Muse for Mac came
out today? Hold on. There's a note here
that Muse for Mac came out today.
That might be why I haven't gotten my
hands on it yet.
Meta's Muse hits Mac. Ah, three days
ago. Ah,
okay. So, that's why I haven't seen it
yet. Okay. Desktop app came out. Anyway,
to me, this is an $1,800 stock. There's
so much money in uh Meta. So, I've got
Meta at basically an $1,800 price
target.
Uh if I go look at, let's do AMD and
some of these other plays right now. Uh
Nvidia, I'm looking at over 600 bucks
for that stock when and yes, that will
make it probably the first 10 trillion
company. And frankly, it deserves it. If
I look up
AMD,
we are at 747,
which means right now we are trading for
82 times
uh 82 times and then the growth rate is
this is the current projection divided
by 4 55 82 divid divided by 55. Yeah, it
puts me about 1.5 times. That's what we
were saying earlier. That still gives it
upside though. Its margins are nowhere
near as good as Nvidia, so you do have
to give it a little bit of a lower
upside uh on a PEG ratio basis, but this
would still justify about a $944 stock.
So, you can see a lot of stocks like an
Nvidia I think has has doubled. I think
Meta's got an easy double in it. To me,
AMD actually still has 50% up on it. Oh,
it's just got a lot of momentum right
now. Okay,
that clarifies those price targets. I
know some folks had questions about
that. Uh let's take a look here at uh oh
yeah, another thing. AMD Venice, which
is one of their latest products, is
expected to deliver 2.8x more agents per
watt than Vera. Now, in fairness, we're
comparing a newer to an older, so
there's still some work to do, although
Vera is still a relatively new chip for
Nvidia. But this is this is the horse
race aspect. We talked about Helios, so
the rack system. Nvidia probably wins on
full rack system. And there's such a
shortage that they honestly they all win
though, so it doesn't matter. Talked
about Intel. We talked about ARM. We
talked about the $20 billion guide on
CPUs from Nvidia, which is bullish. Just
remember the growth rates are probably
going to look higher at Nvidia because
they're coming off of a zero base. So
you're coming off like infinite growth
basically. And now Jensen's coming out
saying, "Yeah, the 70% growth we were
expecting for the whole business as a
whole is probably going to end up being
a double." Originally there was a supply
constraint issue. Uh the other thing
I've talked a lot about this regarding
memory as well.
Current GPUs are getting so efficient at
processing bandwidth that they don't
need as much high bandwidth memory. But
but but but but there is something to be
said about a gentic AI that is actually
different. So we got to touch on this.
This is important. Okay. So we're going
to draw this out together. Let's say you
have
I'm just going to I'm just going to use
the Blackwell 6000 just because I know
it has 96 gigabytes. I think the Reuben
uh Rubin's like 228, isn't it? Whatever.
I'll just use that. Let's go call it 228
gigabytes of RAM. Okay, I might be off
by a few gigabytes there, but let's say
we have 228 gigabytes of RAM on a Reuben
chip.
For an LLM, you might only need to
actually run a Frontier LLM. You might
only need this portion right here. So,
we'll call this the Frontier LLM loaded.
Okay.
Uh now the thing that makes AI
hallucinate less is having context.
Okay, context goes right here.
Okay, so this is the model.
This is the model portion of your uh
VRAMm. This is your contextual portion.
Most text change text chains today are
not really hitting a memory wall
anymore. Uh so what happens is you're
you're kind of filling up like maybe
this which means you actually have a lot
of what's called stranded RAM. You're
just not using this section. So now
there's something especially important
for agent to compute which is actually
bullish for memory is you come in and
say all right well we're not going to
let all of this be stranded since we've
already loaded the model layer and we
can accomplish this with one set of
agent to compute what can we now do when
we have all this extra headroom which is
actually bullish for high bandwidth
memory like your skinex's or your micron
we can run what's called parallel
processing and we could go in here and
say this will be agent, you know, if
this is agent one, this could be agent
2, agent three, agent four, agent five.
And so now they're all running that LLM
model that has been loaded, but we are
actually doing and running five
different
uh contextual outputs at the same time.
So, your chat could be here, Kevin's
chat could be here, your mom's chat
could be here, your daddy's chat could
be here, and your coupon code chat could
be right here. Okay? So, you could get
five different agents running on these
these, you know, higher RAM chips. And
so just because there is this fear of
stranded compute uh which is true on the
frontier training side, it's worth
having this offsetting argument that a
gentic AI can actually help you make use
of that stranded RAM which then
helps lead to more enthusiasm about DRAM
prices going up. DRAM prices are up like
95% in Q126, right? They're projected to
go up. H it's going to slow down.
They're probably going to peak out on
pricing growth by the end of 27 because
you're getting a lot more supply coming
online. DRAM does end up being a
commodity. But I mean in fairness, all
three of the DRAM makers are sold out of
high bandwidth memory. And SKH Highix's
I think comes online last in like 2028
or 2029. So you've got a lot of work to
do. So there's there's still time for
the memory plays as well. So that is
another beneficiary of the AI stack for
uh for agents. So think about for a
moment all of these opportunities for
making money on agentic AI when we're
really like how many people do you know
are using agents? It's probably a
fraction
of the people who could be. So I think
we're really early on this phase. We're
early for Meta. We're still early for
AMD though I think it's overbought in
the short term. early for Nvidia, which
is crazy to say because it's a $5
billion dollar company, which means it's
early for Intel, it's early for ARM. Uh
it's the memory stocks I'm a little bit
more torn on. I could see the argument
for it. I'm a little bit more torn on
memory.
Uh and uh and it's early for the
advertisers, the advert. I mean, people
everybody's going to end up having
Grockbot and all this stuff. I actually
think that's why SpaceX I think was down
like a percent today because Meta did so
well. You know, people are like, "Oh,
everybody's going to Metamuse. That must
be bad for uh for SpaceX. It's a horse
race. It doesn't really matter." You
know, the ultimate winner is the ones
selling the chipsets. I feel like uh and
and that seems to be AMD and Nvidia at
the moment, but this is pretty
incredible. So, uh this is not a boom
that is near end cycle. I know some
people like, "But Kevin, you made a
video that said two paths to recession."
I did. And in it, I said, I'm buying the
dip because there are no signs of the
two path to recession, two paths to
recession, but we should be aware of the
two paths to recession so we can be
watchful and know when things U-turn.
That's the big red flag. So, join me
over at meetke.com. Use that coupon code
metaballs.
One more thing I'm going to note. I just
want to thank you all for being here. I
mean, I don't know who makes it to the
end of like a long yap on uh AMD and and
agents. If you made it, you'll have to
leave a comment. But thank you so much
for being here and supporting. Over the
last month, we've been cranking out way
more content. I've been having more fun
than ever posting to YouTube. Our views
are almost triple what what they were.
Our impressions are triple. Our views
are more than double heading towards
triple uh what they have been in the
past. And so uh we're doing great. You
know, it's helping it's helping the
startup grow. Uh it's helping the
channel grow. And I'm having a lot of
fun providing this insight and
information. And it's also, I think,
making our alpha report better by the
day. Uh, just the more involved we are,
the more we're seeing out there and the
more we're able to incorporate into uh
the calls that we're making. Obviously,
can't be perfect. Not always perfect,
but I think so far we are we are
crushing uh uh the W's. Uh so, I'm I'm
really excited about that and I hope
you're able to benefit from those. And
so, as always, I'll fall on the sword
for you so you can go make money. Oh
man, your poor Kevin just lost lots of
money. Oh, but that's okay. I am with
you. With you. Oh man, your poor Kevin
just lost lots of money. Oh, that's
okay. I am with you.
Here we go. Come on. Push it. Buy the
dip. Buy the dip. Here we go.
Why not advertise these things that you
told us here? I feel like nobody else
knows about this.
>> We'll we'll try a little advertising and
see how it goes.
>> Congratulations, man. You have done so
much. People love you. People look up to
you.
>> Kevin Praath there, financial analyst
and YouTuber. Meet Kevin. Always great
to get your take.